

ABOUT ME

I am 24 years old, currently in my fifth year as an Industrial Engineering student, in the lookout for new challenges that will help me develop both professionally and personally. I am proactive, enthusiastic, and pragmatic. I look forward to working within an environment where I can provide my set of skills, as well as learning from my work team.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

LOCATION:

Buenos Aires, Argentina.

CONTACT INFO

PHONE:

+(549) 11 3356-7468

EVVVII.

mateomarco.gon@gmail.com

LINKEDIN:

www.linkedin.com/in/mateomarco

PERSONAL WEB:

mateomarco.github.io/

GITHUB:

github.com/MateoMarco

MATEO MARCO

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree

2018 – Present University of Buenos Aires Industrial Engineering

High School Degree

2013 - 2017

St. Brendan's College.

Bilingual Degree with specialization in Exact Sciences

LANGUAGE CERTIFICATIONS

International Advanced Subsidiary Levels (AS Levels) | 2017 University Of Cambridge

International General Certificate of Secundary Education (IGCSE) | 2016 University Of Cambridge

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ExitBuilt | Jr. Web Developer

2023.10 - Present

Development and maintenance of innovative web applications. Contributing to the entire software development lifecycle, from coding and testing to debugging, my responsibilities include troubleshooting software issues and actively participating in the continuous improvement of processes.

ExxonMobil | Sales Operations US

2023.03 - Present

Product Solutions Intern for Fuels US, designing and deploying automated workflows that optimize and enhance streamlining processes with Python, API integration and tools as UiPath, Alteryx.

CONFERENCES & COURSES

Latin-Iberoamerican Conference on Operations Research | 2022Development of an algorithmic model to grade Operations Research exams based on Artificial Intelligence, using Python and R, presented at Faculty of Exact Sciences and implemented in examinations.

KEY SKILLS

- R | Intermediate
- Python | Intermediate
- **SQL** | Intermediate
- VBA | Advanced
- HTML, PHP, JavaScript, CSS | Intermediate